<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Website of Daniel Escudero on Personal Website and Blog</title>
    <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Website of Daniel Escudero on Personal Website and Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://deescuderoo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Daniel Escudero   This website is still under construction
 Hello! Welcome to my homepage. I am Daniel Escudero, I started in May 2017 as a PhD student at the Cryptography and Security group at Aarhus University, Denmark. I&amp;#39;m currently working under the supervision of Ivan Damgård, Jesper Buus Nielsen and Peter Scholl. I obtained my Bachelor&amp;#39;s degree in Mathematics from Universidad Nacional de Colombia in 2016 where I had the valuable opportunity to work in a research project on Multivariate Public Key Cryptography during the last two years of my studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptoday</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/cryptoday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/cryptoday/</guid>
      <description>Program  (10.30 - 10.55) Perfectly Secure and Perfectly Correct Oblivious Parallel RAM with Sublinear Worst-Case Bandwidth Overhead    Adam Blatchley Hansen
    (10.55 - 11.20) Optimal Oblivious Priority Queues    Zahra Jafargholi, Kasper Green Larsen and Mark Simkin
    Abstract: In this work, we present the first asymptotically optimal oblivious priority queue, which matches the lower bound of Jacob, Larsen, and Nielsen (SODA&amp;#39;19).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/dissemination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/dissemination/</guid>
      <description>A Crash Course on MPC  I am working on a series of posts explaining MPC from the ground up. These can be found in our blog, The Sugar Beet: Applied MPC.
 The following are the current posts online:
  Part 0, Introduction
  Part 1, Basic Terminology and Essential Results
  Part 2, Two-Party Computation using Beaver/Multiplication Triples
  Part 3, Shamir Secret-Sharing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/other/</guid>
      <description> Music  I enjoy playing and composing music.
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Peer-Reviewed Publications  2021    Fantastic Four: Honest-Majority Four-Party Secure Computation With Malicious Security
  Authors: Anders Dalskov, Daniel Escudero and Marcel Keller
  ACNS 2021
    Secure Training of Decision Trees with Continuous Attributes
  Authors: Mark Abspoel, Daniel Escudero, Nikolaj Volgushev
  PoPETs 2021
    An Efficient Passive-to-Active Compiler for Honest-Majority MPC over Rings   Authors: Mark Abspoel, Anders Dalskov, Daniel Escudero and Ariel Nof   ACNS 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>2020    Efficient Protocols for Oblivious Linear Function Evaluation from Ring-LWE
  TPMPC 2020: Theory and Practice of Multi-Party Computation Workshops
  Virtual Conference
  June 2020
    PRIMAL: A Framework for Secure Evaluation of Neural Networks
  OpenMined Privacy Conference
  Virtual Conference
  September 2020
    Efficient Protocols for Oblivious Linear Function Evaluation from Ring-LWE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve been a teaching assistant in the following courses.
  Machine Learning (Aarhus University, fall 2020)
  Computer Architecture, OSs and Networking (Aarhus University, spring 2019 and spring 2020)
  Distributed Systems and Security (Aarhus University, fall 2018)
  Computability and Logic (Aarhus University, spring 2018)
  Machine Learning (Aarhus University, fall 2017)
  Vector and Analytic Geometry (UNAL, 2016)
  Basic Mathematics (UNAL, 2015)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
