<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Website of Daniel Escudero on Personal Website and Blog</title>
    <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Website of Daniel Escudero on Personal Website and Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://deescuderoo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Daniel Escudero Hello! Welcome to my homepage. I am Daniel Escudero. Since September 2021 I am a cryptography researcher at JP Morgan AI Research. Prior to this, starting on May 2017 until August 2021, I was a PhD student at the Cryptography and Security group at Aarhus University, Denmark, working under the supervision of Ivan Damgård, Jesper Buus Nielsen and Peter Scholl. I obtained my Bachelor&amp;#39;s degree in Mathematics from Universidad Nacional de Colombia in 2016 where I had the valuable opportunity to work in a research project on Multivariate Public Key Cryptography during the last two years of my studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissemination</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/dissemination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/dissemination/</guid>
      <description>A Crash Course on MPC I am working on a series of posts explaining MPC from the ground up.
The following are the current posts online:
Part 0, Introduction Part 1, Basic Terminology and Essential Results Part 2, Two-Party Computation using Beaver/Multiplication Triples Part 3, Shamir Secret-Sharing Part 4, Honest-Majority MPC with Passive Security Part 5, Error Detection and Error Correction Part 6: MPC with Active Security for t&amp;lt;n/3 Part 7: Honest-Majority MPC with Active Security Part 8: Two-Party MPC with Active Security An Introduction to Secret-Sharing-Based Secure Multiparty Computation I&amp;#39;m in the process of writing an accessible, comprehensive and self-contained introduction to (secret-sharing) based multiparty computation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/music/</guid>
      <description> Music I enjoy playing and composing music.
Daniel Escudero · Daniel Escudero </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Peer-Reviewed Publications 2023 SuperPack: Dishonest Majority MPC with Constant Online Communication
Authors: Daniel Escudero, Vipul Goyal, Antigoni Polychroniadou, Yifan Song and Chenkai Weng Eurocrypt 2022 Link 2022 Vector Commitments over Rings and Compressed Sigma-Protocols
Authors: Thomas Attema, Ignacio Cascudo, Ronald Cramer, Ivan Damgård and Daniel Escudero TCC 2022 Link Fast Fully Secure Multi-Party Computation over Any Ring with Two-Thirds Honest Majority
Authors: Anders Dalskov, Daniel Escudero and Ariel Nof CCS 2022 Link TurboPack: Honest Majority MPC with Constant Online Communication</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminar</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/seminar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/seminar/</guid>
      <description> At AlgoCRYPT CoE, we run weekly seminars on topics related to Cryptography. If you want to give a talk, please contact me.
Time Tuesdays 12.00-13.00 EST
Location Remote https://jpmchase.zoom.us/my/escudero (You will be placed in a waiting room)
In person 383 Madison Avenue, New York City. Please contact me if you plan on attending in person since we need to register you and let you in.
Schedule Nov 23th
Threshold-Optimal MPC With Friends and Foes Nikolas Melisaris — Aarhus University Nov 29th Dec 6th Dec 13th Dec 20th Dec 27th (break) Jan 3rd (break) Jan 10th Jan 17th Jan 24th Jan 31th Feb 7th </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>2022 SuperPack: Dishonest Majority MPC with Constant Online Communication
CCS 2022 Los Angeles, USA November 2022 More Efficient Dishonest Majority Secure Computation over Z_2^k via Galois Rings
CRYPTO 2022 Santa Barbara, USA August 2022 Fast Fully Secure Multi-Party Computation over Any Ring with Two-Thirds Honest Majority (Invited Talk)
International Conference on Coding and Cryptography (ICCC) 2022 Virtual Event May 2022 2021 Improved single-round secure multiplication using regenerating codes
Asiacrypt 2021 Virtual Conference December 2021 Information-Theoretically Secure MPC against Mixed Dynamic Adversaries</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://deescuderoo.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deescuderoo.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description> I&amp;#39;ve been a teaching assistant in the following courses.
Machine Learning (Aarhus University, fall 2020) Computer Architecture, OSs and Networking (Aarhus University, spring 2019 and spring 2020) Distributed Systems and Security (Aarhus University, fall 2018) Computability and Logic (Aarhus University, spring 2018) Machine Learning (Aarhus University, fall 2017) Vector and Analytic Geometry (UNAL, 2016) Basic Mathematics (UNAL, 2015) Linear Algebra (UNAL, 2014) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
